Hello, a very hearty
welcome to my YouTube channel
Frequency and I will be joining you right now
today we will talk about the IPL, the
IPS of life is as special as
some of the IPL matches, the
rising cases of Corona have increased the concern, the
insurance company has made six major changes,
so we will talk about which policy will
double your time in 2 years, we will talk about
which 5 best health insurance policies of the
new era, to deal with the expenses of Reno Polona, ​​there will be
mask and cover in just a single policy,
mental disorder has increased in the Corona period, will it be
covered in the disease or not, which
diseases will be covered, definitely very special
for you because in medical store sheet
charges, was there no institute earlier, thank
you, what were the
expenses you had to pay during the exclusion plan,
lastly also tell me
whether there has been any change in your room rent,
I will keep bringing you videos as well, take a
playlist of some videos in the i button,
do press the like button to subscribe to the channel so that
you remain informed about the upcoming videos  And keep getting further knowledge
from such videos, let's
start with this, it is very well said
that medicine is the heart's desire to live a peaceful life,
if we make it a habit and take care of
animals then life automatically becomes beautiful,
from October 1st the biggest
change that has come in the help college due to Karuna is
that diseases like neuro-related disorders will
also be covered in your health
insurance, the disease that happened four years ago, the
pre-existing 2G scam will be covered,
mental genetic diseases will also be covered in it,
seventh more diseases will be
covered in health insurance, you will
not have to make any separate payment for this, it will be
covered in your health policy itself, the
biggest thing is that yes, here one more your
premium may increase by 10%,
but the
company has tried to cover your diseases as much as possible, now
secondly the expenses like pharmacy, from
going to the hospital to
coming back, the expenses that used to be incurred, on the pharmacy, on
your medicines, those expenses will also be included
in it, some associate expenses were also
considered like from being Bigg Boss to
your diagnosis  The expenses that were taken till the
treatment of your Big Boss disease would
also be included in your policy. These
expenses will not be borne by you.
One big and major advantage is that
customers will be able to run more than one policy. Nice,
I will tell you here which mistake is this
which is covering Corona. The
cost of telemedicine will also be a part of your claim.
Secondly,
if you had any VS exit
etc. four years ago, it was already covered in the critical illness,
but now even after three months, if it is
deducted, then it will still be
considered as an existing disease. This is a matter to be noted.
And for those whose policy is already a mediclaim policy, there is a big good
news for them that if any
kind of claim comes, from pre-existing to
any disease, there is a claim for a
disease like cancer, at
least then that too for any organ slaughter. If
you have made a policy for critical illness
and
you will definitely get coverage up to your limit, in these changes your
Most of the diseases
are covered but since the policy is already in operation for eight years,
you do
n't need to get a separate policy. All diseases are
covered under it.
You also need to pay the maximum room rent, which
you can report earlier. Policy holders who already have a
policy are at an advantage. I have
made more videos for you
on Mediclaim. I will go to them and
put them in the playlist. You
can switch on the checklist in them to see what a health
policy will do for you. Let's talk about this
new age new insurance policy.
Your time in the policy will double in 2 years.
Such a policy is Max Bupa's
Rehabilitation Computer Policy, in which your
sum doubles after 2 years
because if you don't take the plan,
50% of it is deducted. This
is a company in which you have a 50% add-on for your no
claim bonus, hence your time savings double.
Now we will talk about which five different
health policies can
benefit you. One health policy is
Max Bupa's Rehabilitation and this  Whatever the company used to
issue earlier, store it there and this is the
Jhal
Ki Mitti Advantage Policy. In this,
your SMS increases, there is also a no claim bonus for
leave, plus there are many more
advantages in this that you will get all types of claims in this, there will be
no reaction and it will take
thirty minutes, whatever the premium is, that too within
your budget. So
Religare has launched a policy with MetLife, the
fourth policy is that you will get a new
Delhi. Currently, ICICI has launched a policy with lines,
so let's chart out the
5 policy which I
told you and for any information, you
can follow us on WhatsApp, you can follow us on Facebook, you
can do this program, there is some
plan or the other, you must
keep it in your pocket, keep it switched on, I will tell you that you
can watch more of my videos on health insurance in the i button and take care of your health first
and protect yourself,
stay healthy and happy.